It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
The atmosphere has changed, somehow.
雰 囲気変わったね、なんか
I feel like I've grown up.
なんか大人びた感じになった
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Feels good.
いい感じ
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてる?
cooked rice?
ご飯?
I haven't eaten it yet.
まだ食べてないです
After that, let's have something to eat and then go.
そしたら、なんか軽く食べてから行こうか
please.
どうぞ
My hair color was quite flashy before,
髪色も前、結構なんか派手な色だったから、
I wish it felt more calm.
なんか落ち着いた感じになったらいい
Yeah.
うん
It's been half a year since I last saw you, so I'm really tired.
なんか、半年ぶりだからめっちゃごふんすね
After taking a bath.
お風呂入ってからね
Let's take a bath.
お風呂入ろう
Maybe I can't resist going to the bathroom.
多分、お風呂行っても我慢できないもんね
I'll do it in the bath.
お風呂でしちゃう
Shall we do it?
しちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Did you lose weight by taking a bath?
お風呂に痩せた?
I wonder if I lost weight.
痩せたかなぁ
Have you lost weight?
痩せた?
Yeah.
うん
I've lost weight, or rather, I've become more mature-looking.
痩せたっていうか、体付き大人っぽくなったね
Yes, I lost weight.
はい、痩せた
It's been a while since I last saw her, but she seemed so mature and cute.
久々だったけど、めっちゃ大人な感じになって可愛かったなぁ